Thanks for watching!
The kettle and the idol
I'm not sure if I would say it myself, but I think I'm a girl in a box,
I can't ride a bicycle,
The other day, for the first time, I was invited to ride a bicycle on TOKU's YouTube project,
I was able to go about 1 meter on the bike,
Since then, I haven't had a chance to ride a bicycle,
There was also a manga that I was not allowed to read until I was 20 years old.
I was not allowed to read any manga until I was 20 years old, like Gob of Jojo's Bizarre Adventure,
Gob from JoJo's Bizarre Adventure, and Sword of the North Star,
I was told by my father that I could not read those until I was 20 years old,
But I finally turned 20.
So I'm really excited now.
I'm excited to be with you.
What's the reason why you were not allowed to read those books until you turned 20?
Reason? I don't know, I haven't read it myself,
Maybe there are grotesque or extreme expressions? No?
I don't know, but I think it's a bit grotesque and a bit extreme,
I don't know,
You can read it when you turn 20 years old.
So, you are saying that the secret dance was prohibited until the age of 20, right?
So you are going to lift the ban on secret dances from now on?
Yes, that's right.
When they start using "secret dance," they say they have started reading it.
And the chef, too.
I think it would be good if they think they can read it,
Or cooking, for example,
I think it would be good for the chefs to think that they can read,
Is there a rule against cooking or using fire?
Or that you have never used a fire before?
I got burned when I made pancakes before,
After that, I was banned from cooking in Japan,
So, even though you turned 20, the ban has not been lifted?
I don't think so.
But I think it's about time I did,
What can you do with a knife?What can you do with a knife?
I've never used a knife before,
It's a little dangerous.
I've been told it's dangerous.
What about when you go to your friend's house?
I can't even go to my friends' houses,
I was the type of person who would never go to a friend's house,
Did you ask them to come?
No, I never asked them to come.
I stayed over only once in high school.
Wow.
That's right.
So I didn't do anything active like that.
Did you ever go out with other members of the group?
There were many family restaurants that I had never been to.
There were many family restaurants that I had never been to before, and I was going there for the first time with Toku-san.
But I thought it would be dangerous if I told her,
I try not to say too much. In front of the members.
I don't think I can say that I've never been there before,
It was my first time, so I didn't know how to order,
I was like, "You're going to do that? I was like, "I've never been there before.
How was it to be an idol between you and the girls in the box?
Are you glad you did it because you had nothing to do?
Yes, I am. But I'm absolutely sure of what my mom says.
My mom said, "Why don't you try idolizing? She said, "Why don't you try idolizing?
So I decided to give it a try,
But as it turned out, I succeeded,
I feel that what my mom says is absolute.
I see. So you were recommended by your mother, and it just came out of your mouth.
That's right. I could expand on the name, so I thought I'd give it a try.
Lastly, please give us a cute closing statement.
This program is
Mr. Kesuke
and Doron
Hatsumi
Rimokenprofit motive
Mr. Ikuma
Thank you very much for all of your support!
Thanks a lot!